國土安全
第三季 第八集
美國空軍及海軍
Air and naval forces of the United States
對恐怖組織發起了一系列攻擊
launched a series of strikes against terrorist facilities...
泛美航空103號班機于洛克比失事
Pan Am flight 103 crashed into the town of Lockerbie.
他已批準在非洲  歐洲和中東的恐怖行動
He has sanctioned acts of terror in Africa, Europe, the Middle East.
我們不容科威特遭受侵略
This will not stand, this aggression against Kuwait.
對于恐怖襲擊的不懈打擊
This relentless pursuit of terror.
我們將一視同仁
We will make no distinction...
美國軍艦科爾號
The USS Cole was attacked
在亞丁灣港口加油時遭到襲擊
while refueling in the port of Aden.
這是恐怖主義行動
This was an act of terrorism.
這是可鄙懦弱的行動
It was a despicable and cowardly act.
下面為您演奏的
The next samba we're going to swing for you
是一首經典曲目
is one of the good old favorites.
直到他受到了阻擊
...until something stops him.
整個事件就發生在我的眼前
It was right in front of my eyes,
而我絲毫沒預料到
and I never saw it coming.
該飛機撞向了世貿中心
That plane crashed into the World Trade Center.
成千上萬的民眾東奔西逃
Thousands of people running.
我們必須  也將在國內外保持警惕
We must and we will remain vigilant at home and abroad.
你是我見過最聰明
You're the smartest and the dumbest fucking person
又最愚蠢的人
I've ever known.
我不是不明真相的那個人
I'm not the one who got it wrong.
我是唯一的明白人
I'm the only one who got it right.
拿下
Take 'em.
通通拿下
Take 'em all.
《國土安全》前情提要
Previously on homeland...
我是本尼特  帕爾和漢莫爾頓事務所的律師
I'm an associate at Bennett, Parr and Hamilton.
我們的一個生意伙伴想見見你
One of our partners would like to meet with you.
麥吉森小姐  我是利蘭·本尼特
Miss mathison, Leland Bennett.
你的客戶想要什么
What does your client want?
他們想時不時借用你的大腦
To pick your brain from time to time.
要保持你大腦的正常運作
Put you on retainer as it were.
別出聲
No sound.
拿下來
Take it off.
卡莉·麥吉森
Carrie Mathison.
現在我們來說說納賽爾·赫佳茲
It's time we talk about Nassir Hejazi.
你用這個名字從革命衛隊中挪用了4500萬美元
Whose name you used to embezzle more than $45 million.
你現在成了自己國家的敵人
You are now an enemy of your own state.
我已經為你計劃好了
I got plans for you.
什么計劃
What plans?
我要把你放回伊朗
I'm gonna play you back into Iran.
從現在起  你為我們做事
From now on you work for us.
為我做事
For me.
我招募了一名高級伊朗情報人員
I've recruited a high-level iranian asset.
馬吉德·賈瓦迪
Majid Javadi.
中央情報局恐怖爆炸事件的策劃者
The man who financed the bombing of the CIA.
我們已經談過
We talked about this.
你得摒棄你那套冷戰時期的狗屁理論
The need to wean you of your cold war bullshit.
這是可以扭轉一切的行動
This is a once in a lifetime operation
一輩子就這么一次機會
that can transform everything.
扭轉中東的整個局勢
The entire Middle East.
你說得像嗑藥嗑多了似的
You sound like you're fucking high.
你走之前我得問你件事
I need to know something before you leave.
我必須知道
I need to know...
炸彈是誰放的
Who's responsible for the bomb?
你知道他問了我什么
You know what he asked me?
誰轉移了炸彈
Who moved the bomb?
如果是布洛迪干的
If it was Brody.
那他為什么那樣問我
Now, why would he ask me that?
那似乎在暗示
That implies that there's a difference
該問題存在分歧
of opinion on that subject.
你應該知道是這個人
You should know that the man
放了炸彈  移動了那臺越野車
who built the bomb and moved the SUV,
他并沒有像他們說的那樣死于爆炸
He didn't die in the explosion like they say.
據我所知  他還在美國
As far as I know, he's still in this country.
什么地方
Where?
我不知道
I don't know.
誰知道
Who does?
就是促成我們會面的人
The man that brought us together.
是你的律師  是本尼特嗎
Your lawyer? Bennett?
翻譯：餓得慌  zhanginfo  wdjmhs  慕秋雪  衛老哥
■
翻譯：幸田實果子  川川  我才是怪蜀黍  橫排混血  肉松
校對：慕秋雪  餓得慌  wdjmhs    時間軸：紫熏   憑陵新月
■
后期：餓得慌     監制：wdjmhs
你怎么這么殷勤  我都開始擔心了
What happened to you? I started to get worried.
好久沒機會表現  都生疏了
I'm out of practice.
看著就很好吃  索爾
This looks delicious, Saul.
謝謝
Thank you.
我給你倒杯茶吧
Can I pour you a cup of tea?
好
Please.
你哪里弄到的
Where did you get these from?
這不就是我們
Aren't these the mugs
從菲律賓帶回的杯子嗎
we brought back from the Philippines?
最后的一對
The very last pair.
等事情徹底了結
When this is all over,
我想再回蘇祿海上那座小島
I'd like to go back to that island on the Sulu Sea.
你不必有什么承諾
You know, you don't have to promise anything.
真的  我都明白
Really. I understand.
干嘛不呢
No, I don't see why not.
我們可以開開心心
We might actually have fun.
好吧  畢竟看目前情況
Well, the evidence does seem to indicate
確實有可能成行
that that is possible after all.
你今天可以
Is there any chance
在家待著嗎
that you could stay home today?
求之不得
There's nothing I'd rather do.
不過
But?
不過早晨得去趟白宮
I got a meeting with Mike Higgins
我和麥克·希金斯有個會
this morning at the white house.
-幾點  -九點半
- When? - 9:30.
那我看咱們還有
Well, that gives us an hour and a half...
一個半小時
by my count.
那當然
Yes, it does.
這兒有點問題
Okay, here's something.
馬克西米利安·阿齊茲博士  約旦人
Dr. Maximillian Aziz, Jordanian,
爆炸發生時曾在會場
was actually in the auditorium the time the bomb went off.
外勤還是內勤
Ops or intelligence?
內勤  分析跨國事務
Intelligence-- office of transnational issues.
和利蘭·本尼特什么關系
And what's his connection to Leland Bennett?
他搞了個長篇大論
He wrote a lengthy analysis
研究他們公司背后那些小客戶
of the firm's hip-pocket clients.
伊朗  敘利亞  阿塞拜疆的
Iran, Syria, Azerbaijan.
不過是兩年前
This was two years ago.
基本不符合條件啊
It hardly fits the profile.
受過訓嗎  有沒有爆破經歷
Any munitions training? Experience with explosives?
沒有
Uh... No.
好吧  先加進名單里
All right, add him to the list anyway.
行吧  但我還是想問問
Yeah, which begs the question--
真能確定是那炸彈客挪了布洛迪的車嗎
are we even sure that the guy who made the bomb moved Brody's car?
-看怎么講了  -怎么講
- Depends. - On what?
得看你信不信賈瓦迪
On whether or not you believe Javadi.
反正你信
Which you do.
我是信  但是光憑想當然
Which I do. But it takes more than an opinion
可沒法向索爾交待
to put it in front of Saul.
沒錯
Right.
但我總覺得咱這是在撞大運
You know, I can't help but feel we're spinning our wheels here.
這材料都快被調查局翻爛了
The FBI have been through these files a hundred times.
那天在總部的每一個人
Anybody that was at Langley that day
都被從頭到腳查了一遍
has been turned inside-out and upside-down.
是  但那場爆炸肯定是現場某人搞的
Yeah, well, someone who was at Langley that day did the bombing.
我還是接受不了他們都死掉了
I still can't believe all these people are gone.
我也是
Yeah.
法拉哪兒去了
Where's Fara anyway?
她一個多小時前就該過來
She was supposed to be here over an hour ago.
機密
請進  索爾
Come on in, Saul.
你好麥克  見到你很高興
Hey, Mike. Good to see you.
參議員
Senator?
好吧
Yeah.
參議員的控訴相當嚴厲
The senator's made some serious allegations.
具體是
Which are?
說你把賈瓦迪藏進我們本土的安全屋
That you had Majid Javadi in a safe house, on American soil
還送他出境
and let him go.
這是真的嗎
Do you contest that?
也是  也不是
Yes and no.
是怎么講
What's the yes?
我根本不知曉有任何
I'm not aware of any standing order
逮捕賈瓦迪上校的指令
to arrest Colonel Javadi.
-那你羈押他沒有  -羈押了
- Did you have him in custody or not? - I did.
我操他媽的  索爾
Aw, Jesus fucking Christ, Saul.
我們不光是送他走  麥克
We didn't just "Let him go," Mike.
還盤問了他
We debriefed him.
策反了他
Turned him.
才把他送回德黑蘭
Sent him back to Iran.
策反了他
You turned him?
他是我們的人了
He's ours.
沒法保證他會真的合作
With no guarantee that he'll actually cooperate.
他會的
He will.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
因為我了解他
Because I know the man.
因為他知道游戲規則
Because he knows the game.
這完全是一廂情愿
That is total speculation.
他說得對
He's right.
最近這個部門的工作
We haven't had a whole lot of success
基本沒什么成果
in that department lately.
現在有了  賈瓦迪是中情局史上
Well, we have now. Javadi's the highest placed CIA asset
最有價值的線人
in the history of the agency.
他指揮了總部爆炸案  還提供資金
He ordered and financed the attack on Langley.
那再好不過了  沒人會懷疑他
All the better if he did. He's above suspicion.
公開的抓捕會給伊斯蘭領袖們
A high-profile arrest would've sent a clear message
一個明確的信息
to the mullahs.
都他媽歇菜
Back the fuck down.
但有了線人能讓我們了解
Instead we have a live source, keeping us current
伊朗核武器的最新進展
on Iran's pursuit of a nuclear weapon,
還有全球真主黨的行動
on hezbollah operations all over the globe.
這事我怎么毫不知情
How come I never saw a finding on this?
我們在現場對事件做出反應
We were responding to events on the ground.
必須當場做出決定
The call had to be made in real time.
他心知肚明  這就是鬼扯
That is horseshit, and he knows it.
邁克  該把參議員請走了
Mike, I think it's time you excuse the senator.
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
我是來向幕僚長
I called this meeting to brief
匯報任務第二階段的計劃
the chief of staff on the second phase of the mission.
那你說啊
So, go ahead.
不行  你在場我不能說
I can't. Not with you present.
為什么
Why not?
因為你的密級比"行動級"還低一個等級
Because your security clearance is one level below operational.
你看到他這幅德行了吧
You see what I'm dealing with?
這人根本不服管  失去控制了
The man is out of hand and out of control.
這件事他是對的
And in this case, he's correct.
抱歉  參議員
I'm sorry, senator.
邁克  還有九天
Mike, in nine days,
我就要做局長了
I'm the next DCI.
所以九天后  索爾就會告訴你
And in nine days, Saul will brief you
你需要知道的一切
on whatever you need to know.
但在那之前不行
But not until then.
-邁克  -參議員
- Mike... - Senator.
-邁克  -參議員  請離開
- Mike? - Senator, please.
該死的  索爾
Goddamn it, Saul.
過去一個半月
I spent the last month and a half
我都在給你倆牽線搭橋
arranging a marriage between you two.
我出局了  我知道
I'm out, I know that.
現在成定局了
You are now.
本來不必如此的
You didn't need to be.
為了賈瓦迪  也值了
Javadi was worth it.
算了  跟我說第二階段的計劃吧
All right, tell me about this phase two.
政權更迭嗎
Regime change?
這是最后
Eventually.
我們還在準備
We're setting the stage.
怎么做
How?
首先我們讓賈瓦迪在軍方提升為
First we move Javadi up the chain of command
高級將領
into a senior military position.
怎么做到
How?!
繼續看
Keep reading.
抱歉我遲到了
Sorry I'm late.
路上堵車
Traffic.
我給你點了杯瑪奇朵  但估計都涼了
I ordered you a macchiato, but it's probably cold by now.
謝謝
Thank you.
沒關系
It's fine.
我收到你短信了
So I got your text.
一切都好嗎
Everything okay?
都好
Yes.
不好
No.
是...索爾
It's... Saul.
他怎么了
What about him?
我們做了個決定
We've made a decision.
是我做了個決定
Well, I-I've made a decision.
再給我們的婚姻一次機會
To give the marriage another chance.
我...
I...
要知道  做出這決定我也不容易
You have to know, it's not easy for me.
那你是什么時候決定的
And when, uh, did you decide all this?
昨晚
Last night.
恕我直言  我們昨天還在麗思卡爾頓酒店的套房里
Forgive me, but didn't we just spend yesterday
翻云覆雨
in a suite at the Ritz Carlton?
這是怎么回事
What's changed?
我剛跟你說了
I-I just told you.
怎么  你和索爾突然
What, suddenly Saul and you
決定和好了嗎
have decided to reconcile?
不是事發突然
It's not suddenly.
過去兩個月我們一直在談這事
We've been talking about it for the last two months.
你懂的
You know that.
我之前還以為
Well, I was under the impression
你已經放棄了
That you had given up on that.
你們都放棄了
That you both had.
我也不清楚  也許吧
Well, I don't know, maybe we had.
那你有什么瞞著我
Then there's something you're not telling me.
我和索爾做夫妻都35年了
We've been married 35 years.
我愛你
I love you.
別那樣說
Don't say that.
我很享受和你做愛的感覺
I love making love to you.
-我得走了  -米拉
- I have to go.  -Mira...
再見
Good-bye.
他簽了嗎
He signed off?
這么說吧
Well, let's put it this way--
他認為該行動計劃有可取之處
He sees the merits of the operation.
所以他要讓總統過目
So he's taking it to the President?
-是的  -可取之處
- Yes.  -Merits?
索爾  你他媽是個天才
Saul, it's fucking genius.
還得看能不能落實
If we can pull it off.
你什么時候出發
When are you leaving?
明天早上
Tomorrow morning.
卡莉知道你要出發嗎
Does Carrie know you're going?
她根本猜不到
She can't even suspect it.
你們找我嗎
Heard you were looking for me.
剛剛在看你和賈瓦迪的談話筆錄
Yeah, we were just going over the transcript of your debrief
看看是否與
with Javadi to see if it supported
昨天他對卡莉敘述的內容相符
what he told Carrie on the tarmac yesterday.
結果呢
Which was?
當時移動越野車的嫌犯
That the man who moved the SUV
仍身處在國內
is still in the United States,
并且他和利蘭·本尼特的律所有聯系
And he's somehow connected to Leland Bennett's law firm.
什么聯系
Connected how?
還不清楚
It's unclear.
所以希望你可以指點迷津
We were hoping you could shed some light.
賈瓦迪從未談及與本尼特的關系
Javadi didn't mention the Bennett connection.
那布洛迪呢
Well, what about Brody?
他提及過布洛迪嗎
Did he mention Brody?
在什么背景下
In what context?
背景是他充當炸彈襲擊者
In the context of being the Bomber.
他并沒有詳細地說
Not in so many words, he didn't.
那他怎么說的
Well, what did he say?
他說據他所知  布洛迪沒有移動那輛車
He said as far as he knows, Brody didn't move the car.
據他所知
As far as he knows?
他對我不是這樣講的
That's not what he told me.
-好吧  -他很確定布洛迪不是元兇
- Okay.  -He told me definitively it wasn't brody.
你到底想說什么
What's your point?
他對你我的敘述為何不一致
Why would he tell us two different stories?
你是在詢問我  還是質疑我
Is that a question or an accusation?
我只是希望你可以坦誠地回答
Well, I guess I'd like a straight answer.
如果賈瓦迪提及過布洛迪沒有移動那輛車
And if Javadi even intimated that Brody didn't move the car,
為什么不繼續逼問是誰動的
why not press him on who did?
我估計你生氣是因為
Well, you're angry because I didn't share
我從沒和你談過布洛迪  哪怕是私下里
a conversation with you about Brody. An inconclusive one.
不是  我生氣是因為你似乎完全不在乎
No, I'm angry because you seem entirely indifferent
抓住真正的炸彈襲擊者
to catching the actual bomber.
隨你怎么說  我沒意見
Speak for yourself. I'm all for it.
很高興聽到你這么說
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
這么說  你們倆
So... You two...
已經有計劃了
actually have a plan?
是的  我們想把這家伙給引出來
Yeah, we want to flush this guy out into the open.
怎么做
How?
你和利蘭·本尼特有來往  對吧
You know Leland Bennett personally, right?
我們一起跟國會議員打過幾次球
We've golfed congressional a few times together.
而且我們都是北方基金會董事會成員
And we serve on the board of the northern foundation.
你能很隨意的與他接觸嗎
How comfortable would you be making an approach?
非常隨意
Comfortable enough.
這么早就回來了
Oh, back already?
是的  感覺不舒服
Yeah, I'm not feeling well.
你可以走了
You can go.
今天我來照看他
I'll look after him today.
你確定
You sure?
是的  他怎么樣了
Yeah. How is he?
能坐起來了
Oh, sitting up.
有進步
Progress.
是的  就是有點吃力
Yeah, slowly but surely.
明天見
I'll see you tomorrow.
注意身體
Feel better.
謝謝
Thanks.
老爸
Baba  Joon.
今天我待在家里
I'm staying home today.
[波斯語]
我需要理由嗎
Do I need a reason?
[波斯語]
我不會丟掉工作的
I'm not going to lose my job.
[波斯語]
因為我確定
Because I'm sure.
說英語
Speak english.
[波斯語]
說英語
English.
我來美國不是為了
I did not come to America
像個臟兮兮的阿拉伯人一樣流落街頭
to live in the street like a dirty Arab.
爸爸
Baba...
聽我說
Listen to me.
不會出現那種情況的
Nothing like that is going to happen.
不會有人把我們從家里趕出去
No one's going to throw us out of our home.
別擔心
Don't worry.
我的工作很穩定
My job's safe.
銀行的工作嗎
At the bank?
是的
Yes.
在投行
At the investment bank.
如果你在投行工作
If you work at the bank,
我們怎么會這么窮
Why are we not rich?
里克特  這是個德裔姓氏
Richter. That's a German surname.
我父母出生在漢堡
My parents were born in Hamburg.
你會說德語嗎
Do you speak it?
是的  當然會
Ja natürlich.
很實用
That's useful.
柏林有三家私人銀行是我們的客戶
We represent three private banking houses in Berlin.
能否給我們幾分鐘時間
Would you, uh, excuse me for just a moment?
當然
Of course.
你來早了
You're early.
我正在面試一位準合伙人
I'm in the middle of interviewing a new associate.
我長話短說
It won't take long.
上周基金會開會你沒參加
We missed you at the foundation meeting last week.
沒時間  工作太忙
Couldn't get there. Work.
應該為我們擠出時間
You gotta make time for us.
這個季度我多給你們一百萬還不夠嗎
It's not enough that I've raised over a million dollars this quarter?
你了解我的  從不滿足
You know me. Never satisfied.
不過  我今天來不是為了這事
But... That's not what this is about.
-不是嗎  -不是
- No? - No.
我有不祥的預感
Sounds ominous.
我現在負責反恐工作  順便說下
I do terror now, by the way.
估計你還不知道
I'm not sure you knew that.
我好像真不知道
I don't think I did.
最近看到有你們公司的名字出現
Your firm's name has come up lately.
還不止一次
More than once.
-好事還是壞事  -我不能說
- In what light? - That I can't tell you.
那為什么還告訴我這事
Then why tell me at all?
因為明天早上10點整
Because tomorrow morning at exactly 10:00,
我會參加一個高層絕密會議
I walk into a high level, top secret meeting
而你就是會議的議程
at which you are the agenda.
你想要我干什么
What do you want?
跟我們合作  實話實說
Cooperate with us. Come clean.
避免陷入一場即將升級為...
Get out in front of what's sure to turn into a...
極具傷害性的調查
a bruising investigation.
知道嗎
You know what?
20年前的我也許會被你嚇尿
20 years ago, I might've fallen for that weak shit.
但現在...
But today...
我隨你怎么查
Come after me if you want.
我沒什么好隱瞞的
I've got nothing to hide.
一輛紅色手推車
蠟燭是為誰點的
Who's the candle for?
所有逝去的人
All the departed.
你是東正教徒嗎
You orthodox?
前男友
Old boyfriend.
聽說他之后辦過無數次喜酒
I hear the weddings go on forever.
喜酒的時間比婚姻還長  這笑話能樂一輩子
Longer than the marriages, so goes the joke.
本尼特先生需要你幫他查一個人
Mr. Bennett needs you to look into something for him.
我與馬吉德·賈瓦迪合作  不是利蘭·本尼特
My arrangement's with Majid Javadi, not Leland Bennett.
沒錯
Correct.
但本尼特先生今天得到的消息
But what Mr. Bennett heard today
也許會牽連到你
might reverberate onto you.
牽連我
Onto me?
需要我提醒你嗎
Do I need to remind you--
你已被外國政府招募為特工
You're a recruited agent of a foreign government?
我見過賈瓦迪  一次而已
I met with Javadi. Once.
我同意做他的顧問  而不是做特工
I agreed to consult with him. I'm nobody's agent.
不知道中情局能否理解其中的區別
I doubt the CIA would appreciate the distinction.
你得到什么消息了
What the hell do you know about it?
我知道本律所因為某些原因
I know the law firm appears to be
成為了被質詢的目標
the target of an inquiry of some kind.
這個我可不知道
Well, not one that I'm aware of.
這個警告是經私人渠道傳出來的
The warning was delivered personally,
沒通過官方渠道
outside of official channels.
是在局里工作的人嗎
By somebody who works at the agency?
本尼特先生的老熟人  是的
A longtime acquaintance of Mr. Bennett, yes.
那你想讓我做些什么
So what do you want from me?
確認一下這個報告
Confirm the report.
本尼特先生需要知道
Mr. Bennett needs to know
哪一部分業務處于調查之中
what part of the business is under investigation
以及他能做些什么以求自保
and what he can do to protect himself.
那可不容易
That's not going to be easy.
這么做的話不可能不讓人察覺
Not without setting off alarm bells.
你會想辦法搞定的
You'll figure something out.
讓我想辦法嗎
I'll figure something out?
而且顯然你的時間有限
And obviously there's a clock on this.
顯然極了
Obviously.
喂
Hello?
見效了
It's on.
跟我說說
Tell me.
我剛跟富蘭克林見過面
I just met with Franklin.
他們開始慌了
They're panicking over there.
讓他們慌吧
Well, let them.
等滿24小時
Wait 24 hours...
然后用我們知道炸彈襲擊者的消息給他們一擊
then hit them with the news we know who the bomber is.
好的
Will do.
索爾
Uh, Saul?
什么
Yeah?
在那之前我需要一點私人時間
I need some personal time between then and now.
行
You got it.
-謝謝  -你沒事吧
- Thanks. - You all right?
沒事
Yeah.
我應該早些告訴你布洛迪的情報
I should've shared that intel about Brody with you sooner.
抱歉  我沒考慮周全
I'm sorry, I wasn't thinking.
你死里逃生
You've been to hell and back.
我知道這對你有多重要
I know how important this is to you.
我欠你的  我們都欠你的
I owe you. We all do.
只要我們找到真正的炸彈襲擊者...
Yeah, well, as long as we get the real bomber...
我們會的
We will.
是卡莉嗎
Carrie?
是  你怎么知道的
Yeah. How'd you know?
你的語氣
Tone of your voice.
你從不和其他人那么說話
You don't talk to anyone else like that.
我都沒注意到
Huh, I wasn't aware.
準備開飯嗎
You ready to eat?
要不要開瓶酒
Should I open a bottle of wine?
好主意
That's a great idea.
聽著
Listen...
我得離開幾天
I got to go away for a few days.
是嗎
You do?
-是的  -什么時候
- Yeah. - When?
明天
Tomorrow.
索爾
Saul...
我知道
I know.
時機不太好
The timing's not great.
但你說只是幾天對嗎
But you said only a couple of days?
對  頂多一周
Yeah. A week, at the most.
一周
A week?
要不是我非去不可
I wouldn't be going...
我也不會走的
if I didn't absolutely have to.
我可以跟你一起去
You know what, I could go with you.
-那可真是太棒了  -誰說不是呢
- Wouldn't that be great? - Why not?
這不是什么旅行
It's not that kind of trip.
雖然我希望是
I wish it were.
-干杯  -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
為我們
To us.
你覺得惡心想吐嗎
You've been nauseous?
是的
Yeah.
一般來說現在應該已經沒那感覺了
Usually that goes away by now.
我也是這么聽說的
So I've heard.
我這里看的非常清楚
I'm getting a real clear image here.
你想知道是男孩還是女孩嗎
You want to know if it's a boy or a girl?
不想
No.
很抱歉最后才來找你
Sorry this is so last-minute.
不  很高興見到你
No, no, it's great to see you.
真是個驚喜
This is quite a surprise.
上周我還在院里見到了麥琪
I saw Maggie at the hospital last week,
她什么都沒提
she didn't say a thing.
她不知道
She doesn't know.
這跟你為什么第13周
Does that have anything to do with
才來做第一次孕檢有關系嗎
why you're coming in for your first prenatal exam
其實我沒打算要孩子
I didn't exactly plan this.
但你知道自己懷孕  已經有一陣子了吧
But you've known for some time.
用藥情況如何
What about medications?
你現在在服用哪些藥
What are you currently taking?
現在什么藥都沒吃
Uh, at the moment, nothing.
我知道
I see.
我孕前一個月服用過
I was on 1,800 milligrams of lithium
1800毫克的鋰鹽
for about a month there.
當時事情有點失控
Things were a little out of control.
更早之前
And, uh, before that,
喝了很多酒
There was a lot of drinking.
非常多
A... Lot.
在你知道自己懷孕之后嗎
After you knew?
我還沒想過要去弄一個育嬰室
I haven't been painting a nursery,
就那么放在一邊
just put it that way.
你是告訴我  你想做人流嗎
Are you telling me you wish to terminate?
我只想知道測試結果
I just want to know what the tests say.
是不是都還好
If things are okay.
你缺鐵
You're iron deficient.
這個我們可以補回來
We can fix that.
但是你的血壓非常高
But your blood pressure's very high.
我的工作壓力非常大
I've been... really stressed at work.
你真的應該放松一下
Well, you really should be taking it easy.
是啊  我會試試看
Yeah, I'll try.
卡莉  我們有辦法
Carrie, we can manage this.
保證你和寶寶的健康
Keep you and the baby healthy.
并不神奇  只是一個過程
It's not magic, it's a process.
如果你想要順其自然  決定權在你
You want to leave it to chance, that's up to you.
否則你就需要改變下自己的行為習慣
Otherwise you need to modify your behavior.
不是一周或是兩周  或者方便的時候
Not in a week or two, or when it's convenient.
而是現在
Now.
我現在做的事和孩子父親有關
What I'm doing, it has to do with the father.
我得把事情捋順
I need to make some things right.
這關系到很多人
It matters to a lot of people.
但這不一樣的  卡莉
But this is different, Carrie.
你現在已經不是自己一個人了
You're not on your own anymore.
法拉
Fara?
西拉吉
Sherazi?
你是哪位
And you are?
米切爾·克勞森總長辦公室
Mitchell Clausen. From the I.G.'s office.
什么總長
I.G.?
總監察長
Inspector General.
我能進來嗎
May I come in?
[波斯語]
這邊請
This way.
我可以給你弄點喝的嗎
May I offer you something?
不用
I'm good. Um...
你連續兩天打電話來請病假
You called in sick two days in a row.
是怎么了呢
Is something the matter?
偏頭痛
Migraines.
可是你昨天開車去上班了
Yet you drove into work yesterday.
對
Yes.
你就呆坐在停車場半個多小時
Where you sat in the parking lot for over half an hour
還是決定走了
before deciding to leave again.
我那時候希望頭疼能止住
I was hoping the headache would go away.
所以你才去了
Is that why you then paid a visit
最近發生雙尸案的
to 1426 Longhill Road,
長山路1426號嗎
where the recent double murder happened?
貝塞斯達警局記下了你的車牌號
The bethesda P.D. took down your license number.
警局為了調查這案子
The agency had to call in a lot of favors
召集了眾多幫手
to close that investigation.
你到那兒去會產生嚴重后果
Your going over there jeopardized all that.
我想看看案發現場
I wanted to see where it happened.
為什么
Why?
我很不安
It upset me. I...
我因此煩亂不堪
I was upset by it.
貝倫森局長對你表示出了
Director Berenson has shown an unusual degree
非同尋常的信任  西拉吉小姐
of confidence in you, Ms. Sherazi...
對你委以國家級的重要任務
entrusted you with matters of national importance.
那個我知道
I'm aware of that.
但是你目前的心理狀態
But your current state of mind
使你對局長和中情局的忠誠度
makes your loyalty to him
都有待商榷
and to the agency a very live issue.
轉告局長不用擔心
Tell the director not to worry.
我很好
I'm fine.
明天上班的時候
You can tell him yourself.
你自己跟他說吧
When you come into work tomorrow.
行
Yes.
貝倫森局長
Director Berenson?
這個貝倫森局長是誰
Who is this Director Berenson?
他是我上司
My boss.
他不是銀行里的人吧
But he's no banker, is he?
不是
No.
你依舊執迷不悟是吧
You went ahead, didn't you?
把我的話當耳旁風
In spite of everything I said?
爸爸  發生了恐怖襲擊
Baba, an attack happened.
那又怎樣
So what?
這又不關你的事
It's none of your business.
他們需要有國際金融背景
They needed Farsi speakers
又懂波斯語的人
with experience in international finance.
我必須幫他們
I had to help.
要是那些伊朗特工
And when the secret police find out
發現你為美國人賣命  那怎么辦
who you work for, what then?
我們在德黑蘭還有家人
We have family still in Tehran!
你的叔叔  嬸嬸  侄子
Your uncle, his wife and children.
到時候全部都要上黑名單  被處以絞刑
They will be added to the list of those to be hanged,
或者槍決
or shot!
[波斯語]
我是美國人
I'm an American.
目標身份依舊不明  有可能就是
Target is still unknown, but presumed to be the man
在總部禮堂前安放炸彈的人
who put the bomb in position in front of the H.Q. Auditorium.
這是保羅·富蘭克林
This is Paul Franklin,
現在拿他做木馬  卡莉
our stalking horse. Carrie?
下午晚些時候  我會放出假消息
Later this afternoon, I'll promote misinformation
希望能唬住富蘭克林
to Mr. Franklin in the hopes that
利用他引出炸彈襲擊者
he'll lead us to the bomber.
如果計劃奏效  我們見面之后
Our assumption is that after the meeting,
他會聯系上頭尋求下一步行動指示
he'll reach out for instructions.
也就是這個人
To this man.
利蘭·本尼特  他們律所的一個大股東
Leland Bennett, one of the senior partners at the firm,
因此  本次行動從現在開始
which is why operation, from this moment forward,
針對這兩個人進行
requires a full complement of audio
全程音視頻監控
and visual surveillance on both subjects.
不需要我再重申
I don't have to tell you
抓住這兩個家伙的重要性了吧
what catching this guy would mean.
換句話說  就是不聲張  不妄動  不露面
In other words, stay small, stay cool, stay out of sight.
好  開始行動
Okay, everybody. Game time.
你是對的
You were right.
快說
Tell me.
他們已經把總部爆炸案
They've connected your firm to the guy
牽罪到你們律所頭上了
who detonated the bomb at Langley.
不可能
That's not possible.
就這么告訴你  信不信由你
I'm telling you what I found out.
好吧
All right. Okay.
他們還認為
They're also under the impression
那個炸彈客現在仍在美國
That he's still here in the United States.
是不是真的
Is that true?
回答我  不然的話
Answer the question, or so help me,
我現在就拍屁股走人  你別想再見到我
I'll get up and you'll never see me again.
放松點  卡莉   深呼吸
Take it easy, Carrie. Take a breath.
別把我當孩子哄
No, don't patronize me.
好吧
Okay.
是真的  他還在美國
It's true, he's here.
具體在哪
He's here where?
你這么問就是說他們也沒掌握他的下落
I'm assuming that means they haven't located him yet.
對  他們還沒掌握
No, they haven't.
那他們到底掌握了些什么
Then exactly what do they have?
以同謀罪帶走利蘭·本尼特
A warrant pending before a FISA judge,
面見外國情報監督法法官的逮捕令
naming Leland Bennett a co-conspirator.
這份逮捕令還有多久生效
How soon before the warrant's active?
至少要好幾天
A few days, at least.
他們不會知道的  本尼特做事干凈利落
They won't find anything. Bennett's clean.
他一貫假人之手
He works through a cutout.
就是你
You.
別摻和了  讓我來處理這件事
Just lay low and let me handle this.
一直以來都是你在處理
You're the one who's been handling this,
恕我冒昧  你的話不怎么可信
so excuse me if your assurance isn't very assuring.
他們查到我們朋友了
They have a line on our friend.
他們是怎么知道的
How'd they get onto him?
- 不清楚  -那就去搞清楚
- No idea. - Well, find out.
有點太遲了  你不覺得嗎
It's a little late for that, don't you think?
你確定不是你這出了差錯嗎
You sure it wasn't your mistake?
你確定不是你的錯嗎
You sure it wasn't yours?
我們當時被要求向一名與政府有關系的
We were asked to provide material support
美國公民提供物資支持
to an American citizen with ties to the regime.
并沒有提及他與爆炸襲擊案有關
There was no mention of his involvement in the bombing.
后來提到了
There was later.
你說得對
Yes, there was.
我們當時就該把這個問題解決好
Well, we should've dealt with it then.
也許吧
Maybe.
他們知道他是誰嗎
Do they know his name?
不知道
No.
那我們暫且沒事
Then we're still okay.
你想讓他離開美國嗎
Do you want him out of the country?
是的
Yes.
最好換個新身份
Preferably with a new identity.
我該告訴他多少
How much do I tell him?
無所謂
I don't care.
把他弄出去就行
Just get him out.
富蘭克林發了條短信
Franklin's sending a text.
告訴我
Talk to me.
是個地址  還有時間
It's an address and time.
凌晨一點半在林奇堡的美景汽車旅館
Fairview Motel in Lynchburg, 01:30.
能查到他發給了誰嗎
Can we trace who he's sending it to?
不行  他的手機上一定裝了匿名軟件
No, there must be an anonymizer on the device.
別擔心  卡莉
Don't worry, Carrie.
只要我們盯住富蘭克林
As long as we stick on Franklin,
你就能找到那個炸彈襲擊者
you'll get your bomber.
他說得對
He's right.
我們派一支戰術小隊去汽車旅館
We'll send a tactical team to the motel.
富蘭克林一清理現場
They'll arrest the target
我們就逮捕目標
as soon as Franklin clears scene.
華盛頓特區交通部
D.C. department of transportation
告誡司機朋友們  由于市區街道封閉
is warning drivers to prepare for delays
從星期四至星期六做好延誤準備
due to street closures downtown Thursday through Saturday.
官方稱第十四街西北的南行方向
Officials say southbound 14th Street northwest
G大街與賓夕法尼亞大道之間的路段將被封閉
will be closed between G Street and Pennsylvania.
有情況
Here's something.
可能是他
It could be him.
沒錯  就是他  我看到了
Yeah, it is him. I've got a visual.
收到
Copy that.
他在干什么
What's he doing?
現在就在那干坐著
Just sitting there at the moment.
B小隊  你們看到他了嗎
Bravo, do you have eyes on?
我在屋頂上  監視著他的車
I'm looking down on the roof of his car.
任何人不許動
No one moves
直到富蘭克林離開
until Franklin leaves site.
收到
Copy that.
他在給誰打電話
He's calling someone.
在監聽了
We got it.
你來了嗎
Are you here?
就在外邊
Outside.
閃一下車燈
Flash your lights.
你在哪間房
What room are you in?
先告訴我怎么回事
First tell me what's happening.
你可能被暴露了
You may have been compromised.
他媽的怎么會這樣
How the hell did that happen?
已經發生了
It happened.
怎么發生的有區別嗎
What difference does it make how?
因為要完蛋的是我
Because I'm the one whose life is fucked.
要不是我先找到你
If I hadn't gotten to you first,
你就得蹲一輩子監獄了
you'd spend the rest of your life living in a cage.
你該感激我
Try on some gratitude.
你到底想不想收拾行李走人
You want your exfil package or not?
220號房
2-2-0.
這就來
Be right up.
操  他帶了武器
Shit. He's got a weapon.
什么
What?
他在裝消音器  天吶  你們看到了嗎
Now he's silencing it. Jesus, you seeing this?
他有把槍
He's got a gun!
B小隊  你能確定嗎
Bravo, can you confirm?
不能  我的視野很模糊
Negative. My view is obscured.
他不是要帶走炸彈襲擊者
He's not exfiltrating the bomber,
他要干掉他
he's taking him out.
你沒法確定  卡莉
You don't know that, Carrie.
裝消音器還能有別的原因嗎
Why else would he have a silencer?
她說得對  斯科特
She's right, Scott.
我看到武器了
I make the weapon.
我說了富蘭克林要干掉那個人
I'm telling you Franklin's gonna kill that guy.
聽我說  我們剛聽到本尼特告訴富蘭克林
Listen to me. We just heard Bennett telling Franklin
把那個家伙帶出國境
to get the guy out of the country.
或許本尼特改主意了
Maybe Bennett changed his mind.
不管怎樣  我們得先確保讓富蘭克林繼續行動
Either way, our priority is to keep Franklin in play.
那就任由他殺掉那個炸彈襲擊者嗎
So we just let him kill the bomber?
如果必要的話  是的
If necessary, yes.
我們之前不是這樣定的
That wasn't the deal.
那個襲擊者是唯一可以證明布洛迪清白的人
The bomber's the only way to prove that Brody's innocent.
可是制止富蘭克林會暴露你的身份
And stopping Franklin now would blow your cover
還有賈瓦迪回到德黑蘭的計劃
and Javadi's back in Tehran.
你懂了吧
You get that, right?
在富蘭克林離開前
Until Franklin is clear,
我要求全部小隊停止行動原地待命
I want all teams to stand down.
全部小隊原地待命  收到請回答
All teams, acknowledge standing down.
B小隊  原地待命
Bravo here, standing down.
A小隊  原地待命
Alpha team standing down.
卡莉  收到請回答
Carrie, acknowledge.
卡莉
Carrie?
卡莉  你他媽要干啥
Carrie, what the fuck are you doing?
卡莉  回到車里去
Carrie, go back to the van!
索爾答應過我  會讓這個人活著
Saul promised me this guy alive.
現在這里不是索爾說了算
Saul's not calling the shots here.
他答應過我的  該死  讓他接電話
He promised me, goddamn it. Get him on the phone!
沒有時間  回去
There's no time. Turn around!
卡莉  馬上回去
Carrie, turn around now,
不然我們就要阻止你了
Or we will stop you.
這是對你的最后警告
This is your last warning.
聽他的話  卡莉
Listen to the man, Carrie.
B小隊  我現在授權使用武力
Bravo, I am authorizing force.
開槍射擊  我重復一次
Take the shot. I repeat:
-開槍射擊  -我來
- Take the shot. - Let me.
卡莉  我是奎恩
Carrie, this is Quinn.
快離開
Break away.
對不起  我不能
I'm sorry. I can't.
你會搞死我們的  卡莉
You're fucking us, Carrie.
幾個月的努力  你的努力
Months of work. Your work.
我不在乎
I don't care.
卡莉  我會開槍的
Carrie, I will take the shot.
要來不及了  看在上帝的份上
Window's closing, for christ's sake!
他進去了  富蘭克林進屋了
He's in. Franklin is inside.
把她帶走  趕緊的
Pick her up, for god's sake!
走  快走
Go! Go!
挪開
Move it!
我的老天爺
Jesus christ.
你當時磨蹭什么呢
What was the delay?
我攔住她了  不是嗎
I stopped her, didn't I?
跟她一起走  我來監視富蘭克林
Go with her. I'm watching franklin.
-接通醫院的電話了  -告訴他們
- Hospital's on the line. - Tell 'em we got
有人左上臂受了槍傷
a gunshot wound to the upper left bicep,
大出血  可能是射穿動脈了
significant bleeding, might have clipped an artery.
堅持住  你會沒事的
Hold on. You're gonna be all right.
真該死
Goddamn it!
媽的  他媽的
Fuck! Fuck!
-奎恩  -什么事
- Quinn... - Yeah?
那個炸彈襲擊者死了嗎
...Is the bomber dead?
-死了  -媽的
- Yeah. - Fuck!
他媽的
Fuck!
一定出事了
Something's going on.
-沒錯  你中槍了  -是啊  少廢話
- Yeah, you got shot. Yeah, no shit!
你開的槍
You shot me!
不是  我是說出了別的事
No, I mean, something's going on.
這次行動...這次行動說不通
None of this... none of this makes sense.
呼吸  好嗎  深呼吸  拜托
Just breathe, okay? Deep breaths. Come on.
過來
Come here.
近一點
Come closer.
索爾在他媽什么地方
Where the fuck is Saul?
您的旅途順利嗎
You have a good flight?
還不錯
Yeah, fine.
至少把我送過來了
Got me here.
這邊走
Hey. This way.
在這里等著
Wait here.
再過一個月  這里會更熱的
In another month, it's even hotter.
你想不到有多熱
You won't believe.
或許我會用那一千萬美元裝一臺空調
Maybe I use the $10 million to put in an air conditioner.
在那里
There.